salvagedirect.com 2012-05-20

# QCSA Direct - Privacy Policy

**_QCSA HOLDINGS PRIVACY POLICY_**

QCSA Holdings, Inc.  (“QCSA Direct”) is committed to respecting your privacy.  We take every precaution to protect our users’ personal information.

This policy covers how QCSA Direct treats personal information that it collects and receives, including information related to your past use of QCSA Direct services.  Personal information is information about you that is personally identifiable, such as your name, address, email address, or phone number, and that is not otherwise publicly available.

**_Information Collection and Use_**

You can browse our Site without entering any personal information and thereby remain anonymous during your visit.  QCSA Direct does not collect personally identifying information about users except when you specifically and knowingly provide it.  To use our services, you must register with QCSA Direct using our registration forms.  QCSA Direct collects personal information when you register with us and when you use its services. 

When you register, we may ask for information such as your name, address, email address, phone number, credit card information, business license information, driver’s license information, zip code, and other financial information.  Once you register with QCSA Direct and utilize our services, you are not anonymous to us.

QCSA Direct collects information about your transactions with us, including information regarding items you bid on.

QCSA Direct uses information for the following general purposes: to contact you, to facilitate bidding, buying, and/or selling of items by you through QCSA Direct, to transfer title and ownership of items bought and/or sold by you, and to comply with laws and regulations related to purchases and sales of items by you through QCSA Direct. 

We use you email address, your mailing address, and phone number to contact you regarding administrative notices, new product offerings, and communications relevant to your use of our site.  If you do not wish to receive any or all of these types of communications, you may have the ability to opt out.

We use information in the file we maintain about you, and other information we obtain from your current and past activities on the site, to resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems and enforce our Terms and Conditions.  At times, we may look across multiple users to identify problems or resolve disputes.

**_Information Sharing and Disclosure_**

QCSA Direct does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or nonaffiliated third parties except:

1)      To provide products or services you have requested;

2)      To provide information to parties who work on behalf of or with QCSA Direct under confidentiality agreements;

3)      When you have given us your permission;

4)       When required by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary;

5)      To co-operate with the investigation of purported unlawful activities;

6)      To comply with a subpoena or other legal process served on QCSA Direct;

7)      To protect and defend the rights or property of our customers and visitors to our Site;

8)      To protect and defend the rights or property of QCSA Direct;

9)      To identify persons, who may be violating the law or the rights of third parties.

**_Storage of Information_**

QCSA Direct may store your account information in our databases indefinitely following the termination of your account with us, to the maximum extent allowed by law.

**_Confidentiality and Security_**

We also protect account information by placing it on a secure portion of our site.  Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet is 100% secure.  While we strive to protect your account information, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of such information.  If QCSA Direct learns of a security breach, we may attempt to notify you so that you can take appropriate protective steps.

**_Changes to this Privacy Policy_**

QCSA Direct reserves the right at any time and without any notice to add to, change, modify or update this Privacy Policy simply by posting such change, update or modification on our site.  Any such change, update or modification will be effective immediately upon posting to the site.  Your continued use of this website constitutes your agreement to this Privacy Statement and any updates.

**_Contact Information_**

If you have questions or suggestions, please contact us at:

QCSA Holdings 

42336 Gilbert Drive, P.O. Box 306

Titusville, PA  16354
